<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Justas Dauparas</title>
    <link>https://dauparas.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Justas Dauparas</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2020 Justas Dauparas</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2020 06:44:46 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://dauparas.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>AlphaFold 2 &amp; Equivariance</title>
      <link>https://dauparas.github.io/post/af2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2020 06:44:46 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dauparas.github.io/post/af2/</guid>
      <description>Fabian Fuchs &amp;amp; Justas Dauparas
A few weeks ago, in the latest CASP competition for protein structure prediction (CASP14), DeepMind&amp;rsquo;s AlphaFold 21 outperformed all its competitors with an unprecedented margin. In this blog post, we aim to shed light on one of the important building blocks that distinguishes AlphaFold 2 from the other approaches and likely contributed to their success: an equivariant structure prediction module.
In short: this module is a neural network that iteratively refines the structure predictions while respecting and leveraging an important symmetry of the problem, namely that of roto-translations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn it yourself - online resources</title>
      <link>https://dauparas.github.io/post/learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2020 06:44:46 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dauparas.github.io/post/learning/</guid>
      <description>This is a short list of books and lectures with links for myself and anyone else who might find them useful. A book is worth a thousand arXiv papers!
Machine Learning Books  Pattern Recognition and Machine Learning by Christopher M. Bishop, Information Theory, Inference, and Learning Algorithms by David J.C. MacKay, videos, Machine Learning: A Probabilistic Perspective by Kevin P. Murphy, Bayesian Reasoning and Machine Learning by David Barber, Deep Learning by Ian Goodfellow, Yoshua Bengio, and Aaron Courville, The Elements of Statistical Learning by Trevor Hastie, Robert Tibshirani, and Jerome Friedman, All of Statistics A Concise Course in Statistical Inference by Larry Wasserman, Reinforcement learning: An introduction by Richard S.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>